now we need to add a new item on top of
this list we're gonna call that all
genres so back in our movies component
here in component did mount method this
is where we're initializing the genres
property of the state object we need to
make a slight change here so we define a
new constant genres we set it to a new
array we spread the array that is
returned from get genres function so we
have all the existing genres and then we
can put a new object at the beginning of
this array here we set the name property
to all genres and we don't need to set
an ID because this is not a valid genre
in the database this is just an item on
top of this list okay so now we have an
array of genres we pass that here as the
value of the genres property or we can
simplify the code because the key and
value are the same we can get rid of the
repetition and that is better with this
we get all genres on the top let's
select action we get only the action
movies beautiful now let's go back to
all genres our movies disappear here's
the reason in a render method where we
are filtering the list of movies we're
checking to see if selected genre is
true see if it's true see we're
filtering the movies so we get each
movie and we make sure that the ID of
the genre of that movie equals the ID of
the selected genre in this case our
selected genre doesn't have an ID
because we only set the name property
right that's why we don't see any movies
when we select all genres to fix this
problem we need to change this condition
to something like this select a genre
dot underline ID so if selected genre
and the idea of the selector genre are
both true see then we'll apply a filter
otherwise we get all the movies let's
test out
one more time so we go to action we get
action movies we go to all genres we get
all movies beautiful but there is a tiny
issue here if I go to the second page
and then go back to the action movies we
don't see anything here even though on
the top it says showing three movies
here is the reason let's go back to all
genres as you can see we're on the
second page so when we select another
genre we are looking at the second page
of movies and that genre in this case we
only have three movies or one page in
any of these genres that's why we don't
see any movies in this table to fix this
issue whenever we change the filter we
should reset the page to one so back in
our movies component in handle genres
select method this is where we're
setting the selector genre we should
also reset current page to one this will
fix the spot let's test the application
one more time so let's go to the second
page select action we see all the action
movies comedy all the comedy movies back
to all genres we get all the movies
beautiful